[{"id": 2639, "question": "In Britain arrangements for inviting and entertaining guests at a wedding are usually the responsibility of the bride's family.In most cases it is mainly friends and relations of both families who are invited but when bride's father is a businessman of some kind, the wedding reception may provide a useful occasion for establishing social connections with clients or customers and other people whose goodwill may be of advantage to him.it is, however, the bride's mother who has the job of sending out the formal printed invitation cards. In the case of a church wedding, the vicar of each parish in which the bride and bridegroom live is normally informed about a month in advance of the ceremony so that an announcement of the coming wedding can be made in church on each of three Sundays before i...\n\nQ: What possible difference is suggested between a church and a civil wedding?", "options": ["Civil weddings are less commonly followed by a reception.", "It is less usual for guests to attend the civil wedding formalities.", "Guests at civil weddings are less formally dressed.", "There could be less attention paid at the latter to convention and picturesque effect."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1318, "question": "Recently educators have been questioning \"prep school\" (=preparatory school) where barely literate high school athletes get their transcripts by taking courses occasionally and sometimes by taking no courses at all. The athletes then go on to famous sports universities, where they exhaust their playing years before landing back on the streets without job opportunity or college degrees. The prep school scheme was meant to avoid academic qualification rules for college athletes made years ago by the National Collegiate Athletic Association. The N.C.A.A., which was slow to recognize the seriousness of the problem, has finally adopted policies to root it out. But those policies will not do the job unless everyone is involved, including prep schools and college athletics departments that still ...\n\nQ: From the passage we can infer that   _  .                 .", "options": ["High school students can change their transcripts by transferring to another school or take a lot of courses in one term.", "Transcripts of high school students can be very important reference for students to go to college.", "Most High school athletes can probably be awarded a bachelor's or master's degree after they graduate from universities.", "Transcripts of high school students are so important that they are recorded on metal"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1354, "question": "No one has enough, but everyone has all there is. We each have just twenty-four hours in a day. Time is not our problems , but what we do with the limited time we have is the issue. Many people spend their days on dozens of activities , but achieve very little because they aren't concentrating on right things. The Pareto Principle, also known as the 80:20 Rule shows us that typically eighty per cent of unfocused effort generates only twenty percent of the results. The remaining eighty per cent of the results are achieved with only twenty percent of the effort . To effectively manage your time, you need to change where you are spending your time. We all have the same amount of time every day. How you spend your time is how you spend your life. Here are time management strategies, which may ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, if you want to do several things on Sunday,you should   _  .          .", "options": ["do them while listening to the music", "do all of them at one time", "do the most important one first", "put some of them off till next Monday"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2126, "question": "In America, drivers' education is part of the regular high school curriculum . Every student in his or her second year of high school is required to take a class in driver's education. However, unlike other courses, it is not given during the regular school year. Instead it is a summer course. The course is divided up into two parts: class time for learning laws and regulations, and driving time to practice driving. Class time is not unlike any other class. The students study the basic traffic laws from a text to pass the written driving test that is given to anyone who wants to get a driver's license. Driving time is a chance for the students to get behind the wheel and practice starting steering, backing up, parking, switching lanes, turning corners, and all the other maneuvers required ...\n\nQ: In the last sentence, \"with flying colors\" means   _   .", "options": ["happily", "quickly", "colorfully", "successfully"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 303, "question": "Beginning college is exciting: new ideas to explore, new challenges to be met and many decisions to be made; your future begins here. However, you will find college life is different from your previous school environment. Many of us can be easily overwhelmed by the details of running a well-balanced life. While some of us may have the know-how, I guess there are more of us who can benefit from learning about the experiences of others who have walked the college halls before you. The following you may find of use about life on campus: *Plan well. There are so many new things to do at a new college or university. Give yourself time to make new friends and became familiar with the campus, but don't forget why you are there. Give some time for social activities and manage your time wisely. *If...\n\nQ: According to the passage, why is it exciting to begin college life?", "options": ["Because you will have more freedom at college.", "Because you will no longer be afraid of the beyond", "Because you prepare for your future career and life there.", "Because professors there will provide you with many new ideas."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1432, "question": "1234 PENS is your No. 1 source for promotional pens, advertising pens, and logo pens. We have been in business since 1976, so you can be confident that you're dealing with a trusted name in the industry. Everyone loves a free pen, and by providing your customers with a pen featuring your company name, logo, or message, you can be sure that your company name will always be on their mind! Our custom imprinting service comes at no extra charge, so the price you see is the price you pay for the personalized pens. Do you need pens fast? In a rush for trade shows or a corporate events? Try our 48-hour promotional pens rush service free of charge. We present you with many styles and types of printed pen. Let us know which promotional pen you like and within 48 hours you will have the pens. Want t...\n\nQ: What is special about the pens produced in 1234 PENS?", "options": ["They are designed in 16 styles.", "They come in 48 different color1s.", "Their material is less harmful to the earth.", "Their price is much lower in the pen market."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2733, "question": "The intelligence times provide us much convenience,but at the same time,some of our abilities are being weakened gradually. 1. Memorizing phone numbers It was annoying to remember numbers. Now we simply add them to our contacts list. That usually works well unless our device is lost,stolen,or damaged. No one can be expected to remember all their contact numbers. What we can do is memorize 5 of our most important contact numbers. This should include a mixture of family,friends and business. If you're really ambitious you can memorize 5 contacts for each category. 2. Map-reading skills The convenience and effectiveness of GPS guidance systems and digital maps generated by search engines is unquestionable. They've definitely made our lives easier. What we don't get from using these devices an...\n\nQ: E-readers are thought to weaken our reading comprehension because   _  .", "options": ["they are convenient and can store thousands of books", "they make it more difficult for us to recall information", "less people can afford to buy E-readers", "people are not fond of reading printed books nowadays"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 892, "question": "Going on a road trip? The St. Louis Arch, Statue of Liberty, and Golden Gate Bridge are common great tourist sites. If you prefer offbeat places, check out the following roadside attractions. World's Largest Ball of Paint Alexandria, Ind. In 1977, Michael Carmichael set out to create the biggest ball of paint anywhere. Starting with a baseball as centre, he painted layer by layer of paint day after day, year after year. The ball weighs more than 1,300 pounds, with more than 20,000 coats of paint, which is recognized by Guinness World Record. Visitors can paint the wall themselves and become part of the history. The Museum of Dirt Boston, Mass. The museum is the idea of Glenn Johnson. Labeled glass bottles contain such treasures as dirt from the Great Wall of China, as well as sand from a d...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from the text?", "options": ["Michael must have the largest ball in the world.", "Glenn must have paid a visit to China.", "Ellis could be seen as a pioneer in his time.", "Barry loves ice-cream especially."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3260, "question": "\"Ten years ago I could never have imagined I'd be doing this,\"says Greg Pal,33,a former software executive. \"I mean ,this is essentially agriculture ,right? But the people I talk to, especially the ones coming out of business school , think this is the one hot area everyone wants to get into .\" He means bugs. To be more accurate, the genetic change of bugs---very, very small ones---so that when they feed on agricultural waste such as woodchip or wheat straw ,they do something extraordinary . They excrete crude oil. Unbelievably ,this is not science fiction .Mr. Pal holds up a small cup of bug excretion that could ,in theory ,be poured into the tank of the big Lexus SUX next to us .Not that Mr. Pal was willing to risk it just yet .He gives it a month before the first vehicle is filled up wi...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["it is a very complex process for bugs to produce oil", "it is not worthwhile for Mr. Pal to do the experiment", "it is safe to use the excretion produced by bugs", "it is necessary to use bugs to produce crude oil"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2910, "question": "When I came to Cincinnati as an au pair , a lot of things there were different from what I knew. My host family lived in a huge house I could only describe as a \"castle\".In Germany I had lived in a small apartment together with my mom. Soon I found out that the \"castle\" was actually rather small in our neighborhood. Everybody there was very friendly and polite. They greeted you when they were walking by at least 3 feet away from you. They must not have seen a German au pair before, for most people I met asked me all kinds of questions about Germany. I enjoyed answering their various strange questions. I made a lot of friends and I started to hang out with them. Of course, there were a number of new things, and it took me the whole year to find them all out. I never got homesick. Perhaps it...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE about the author?", "options": ["She lived with her mother in a big house in Germany.", "She never went back to Cincinnati after she came back to Germany.", "She seldom hung out with her American friends as she was too busy.", "She did miss her friends in Cincinnati when she was at the TU-Dresden."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 860, "question": "Nathan's second-hand bike was good enough to get him anywhere he wanted to go. Of course, it couldn't match Tim's in a normal speed race, but all the fancy gears in the world wouldn't get you up Black Mountain. It was so steep in places that you had to get off your bike and push. On this particular afternoon, the odds were all on Nathan's side. First, he was stronger. Tim had always been thin, but recently he'd started to grow so fast that his arms and legs were like pieces of spaghetti. As well as being considerably fitter than his friend, Nathan knew the shortcuts up prefix = st1 /BlackMountain. So when Nathan accepted the challenge, he was sure he'd win. He nearly always did, in competitions with Tim. That was what was strange. Tim was so competitive, and yet he wasn't any good at physi...\n\nQ: What did Tim challenge Nathan to do?", "options": ["test who had the fastest bike", "decide who was the most competitive", "find the secret tracks on the mountain", "race to the top of BlackMountain"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1207, "question": "It was 9:00 am already! Richard had to leave for work! Before leaving he hurriedly looked at the newspaper and stood still! Is he seeing it right? He rubbed his eyes and saw again... Yes, it was his name in the obituary ! He threw the paper in the bin and screamed. Richard started to recollect. He remembered that last night when he went to bed he had a chest pain and he was rushed to hospital. Then he went into a sound sleep. But what happened after that? He could suddenly see his living room filled with people... all in tears; his mom, his wife and his children. He also saw his best friend, the one he had a serious misunderstanding a few days back. He wanted to say \"Sorry\" to him... but now no one could hear his voice. He wondered how he could tell his mom that he felt so thankful to have...\n\nQ: After the dream, Richard would probably   _  .", "options": ["be on good terms with his friend again", "express appreciation and thanks to his friend", "demand an apology from his friend", "break up with his friend"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2725, "question": "Two people have died after two separate university shootings in Texas and Arizona, just hours apart. One person was killed and three injured in the first shooting at Northern Arizona University early on Friday. Later that morning a shooting at a student complex near Texas Southern University left one person dead. In Arizona, police named the gunman there as Steven Jones, an 18-year-old first year student at Northern Arizona University.Mr. Jones told police he was approached by a group of men and attacked. He fled, produced a gun from his pocket and opened fire when the men caught up with him, Arizona police said. Witnesses told police that the victims were unarmed. The second shooting in Texas happened later on Friday morning at the University Courtyard Apartments on the edge of the Housto...\n\nQ: How many people were dead in these two recent university shootings?", "options": ["One.", "Two.", "Three.", "Four."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 519, "question": "It's killed at least two dozen people, damaged hundreds of homes, cost some 22 billion Yuan in direct economic losses so far and has left thousands of family-bound travelers stranded. The massive snow and ice storm that has swept through the southern part of China has put this country into full disaster management mode. Tens of thousands of soldiers have been activated and the government has already provided 126 million Yuan in aide to six provinces in the south slammed by the unexpected winter blast. But is enough being done? And what else can be done to ensure that the effects of natural disasters like the one in southern China are minimized in the future? \"Ni hao, you're listening to People In the Know, your window into the world around you, online at www.crienglish.com here on China Ra...\n\nQ: How many people died from the snow disaster before this report?", "options": ["more than 30", "more than 24", "many", "50"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2091, "question": "The percentage of districts that require elementary schools to teach physical education increased, to 93% last year from 83% in 2000. But just 4% of elementary schools, 8% of middle schools and 2% of high schools provided physical education each school day, as is recommended by the disease control agency. One-fifth of schools did not require physical education at all. In 2004, Congress passed a law requiring each school district to develop a \"wellness policy\" to promote the students' health by setting goals for nutrition education and physical activity. Those policies are just now taking effect, and some school administrators predict that the next survey will show more marked improvements. Some schools have set out to place health education on the same requirement with academics. In Los An...\n\nQ: What excited us most in the survey is that   _  .", "options": ["most schools forbade tobacco use everywhere", "most schools have realized the importance of students' living surroundings", "more schools have set aside daily physical exercise routine", "wellness policy has taken effect"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2116, "question": "Although the weathermen's forecasts for a month ahead are only little better than guesswork, they are now making long-term forecasts into the next century with growing confidence. For the main trend (, ) in the world's climate in the coming years will, scientists say, be a predictable result of man's activities. At the start of the industrial revolution nearly two centuries ago, man set off a big experiment in planetary engineering. Unaware of what he was doing, he spared no thought for the consequences .Today the possible outcome is alarmingly clear, but the experiment is unstoppable. Within the lifetimes of many of us, the Earth may become warmer than it has been for a thousand years. By the middle of this century it may be warmer than it has been since before the last Ice Age. A warmer ...\n\nQ: Long-term weather forecasts beyond the year 2050 may seem strange because  _  .", "options": ["none of us will be alive then", "weathermen cannot even forecast next month's weather correctly", "weathermen can forecast much better than they used to", "no one can stop engineering experiments"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 156, "question": "It is well known that Einstein was the father of the famous Theory of Relativity. But do you know it owes a great deal to Marits, Einstein's former wife? In 1896, 17-year-old Einstein went to Zurich to study physics. There he met a girl from Hungary. They studied in the same class. The same interest brought the two together and the young man fell in love with Marits. In 1903, when Einstein was 24 years old, he married Marits, who was 4 years older than he. After their marriage, Einstein devoted himself to the research of the great theory. To give her husband more help, Marits gave up her own work, and became a good wife and assistant. She tried her best to encourage him whenever possible and she was sure that her husband would succeed. They often discussed the theory while walking outside ...\n\nQ: Einstein and Marits got divorced because   _  .", "options": ["they no longer loved each other", "the 1st World War broke out", "Marits went away with the children", "Einstein had become famous"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1900, "question": "Mary Master man, a senior at West Moore High School in prefix = st1 /Oklahoma City, was named the winner Tuesday of the annual Intel Science Talent Search. More than 1,700 high school seniors across the nation entered the competition, which is in its 66th year. Spectrographs, which measure wave lengths, are used in research such as astronomy and medicine and in industry. For example, they can be used as a sensing equipment to look for explosives or drugs or to help determine how old an art work is through its powders. They can cost as much as $100,000, but Masterman's invention--made of lenses, a laser, aluminum tubing and a camera--cost less than $1,000, Intel said. Masterman received the honor from Intel Corp. Chairman Craig Barrett during a banquet Tuesday night inWashington. \"It was a ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["The competition attracts national talents to attend", "Masterman was sure to win before the contest.", "Intel Science Talent Search is held every year.", "Spectrographs can be widely used in many fields."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2730, "question": "Manchester is the \"capital\" of the northwest of England. Situated on the east bank of the River Irwell, it is a lively busy city with a large student population. Although it was once seen as only a dull industrial place, in recent years Manchester has become the \"in\" place. It is well-known for its clubs, its fashion and its music, not to mention its world -famous football team, Manchester United. There is plenty to see in Manchester and something to suit all taste. For example, you have a taste of the Orient in Chinatown, home to Manchester's large Chinese population. Another place to visit is the historical Eastlefield area, which contains the first urban heritage park in Britain. Here you can walk around the museums and experience the atmosphere of the 19thcentury Manchester. Football f...\n\nQ: What was Manchester like in the past?", "options": ["A small and dull city.", "A city full of factories", "An exciting city to visit", "A popular destination"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3186, "question": "Dreaming is a natural part of who we are. We explore our dreams and develop personal dreams. We even like to dream BIG! For the most part our dreams and wishes focus on the end result. We see ourselves in love, married, driving a great car, on vacation, with tons of money, in a great career, etc. Dreaming about the end result is just fantasizing and wishing. Wishing relies on some magical force to make our dreams turn into reality, and we become unhappy as we're not living our dreams. So how can we make our dreams come true? That is a question we all often struggle with. Even though we struggle with the answer, the answer is not that clear. We make our dreams come true with the action we take. In my opinion, if you dream about being in good health, then change your dream to see yourself wo...\n\nQ: According to the writer, most of the people  _  .", "options": ["pay more attention to developing their dreams", "enjoy the process of their dreams", "are always ignoring the process of living their dreams", "probably dream of making much more money easily"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1618, "question": "Your children's teacher will be providing extra time for test preparation. This school year's test will be held on January 8 and 9. The test preparation time is open to all students, and we strongly encourage your children to attend. This year we are changing the time for our test preparation: it will be on Thursday mornings from 8:10 to 8:50. This helps children who ride the bus and cannot stay for the after-school period. It also helps avoid conflicts with after-school activities. Danielle and Marina will be working with the recent new test takers 6 days on the following Thursdays: 15th, Nov; 29th, Nov; 6th, Dec; 13th, Dec.; 20th, Dec. and 3rd, Jan. Besides the test preparation lectures on these dates, teachers are already putting test preparation into their usual courses. We are finding...\n\nQ: The text is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["how teachers will provide more time for test preparation", "the reason why time for test preparation will be changed", "how teachers have put test preparation into their usual courses", "test preparation information that parents should know about"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2401, "question": "European Work Experience Program(E.W.E.P.)is an independent British organization which began in 1991 in the city of London.E.W.E.P.provides the opportunity for students from the 25 countries of the European Union and nationals from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein to live in England,to gain work experience,to practice their English and to get a better insight into the British social and eulturallife. To apply you must meet the following requirements: *Preferred age: 18 to 28 years old *Be able to work in the UK for a period of at least two months. *Must have a good knowledge of English. *Due to work permit restrictions,European Work Experience Program Ltd will only select you if you are a European Union Member or national from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein. Europ...\n\nQ: You can get in touch with E.W.E.P.by the following ways EXCEPT by  _  .", "options": ["making a teJephone call", "sending the organization a fax", "writing an e-mail to the organization", "going there in person by air"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 815, "question": "What is a lifestyle and how is that different from a life? A lifestyle is about brand names and buying identity or fame. Lifestyle gives a false sense of peace and acceptability that comes from others recognizing what you've bought into (as well as bought). If your car, clothes, and home are expensive, you're sophisticated and stylish. If you have the right kind of job or go to the right social gatherings, then you receive the insincere approval of others. This means that your self-esteem is always at the mercy of others, with no appreciation of you as an individual. A life, on the other hand, is very different. A life is what you lead when you know what matters most to you. It is very simple and comes from being connected to what you know is important and being willing to put that first, ...\n\nQ: Which of the following examples best explains \"what is life about\"?", "options": ["We work long hours in a job that we do not enjoy.", "We focus on what we wear, or what kind of car we drive.", "We find out what our true beliefs and values are and choose to live by these.", "We think that how others see us is more important than what we think of ourselves."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2548, "question": "Hi, everybody. On Friday, I had a discussion with working women in Rhode Island about the economic challenges they face in their own lives--challenges shared by many of you. Thanks to the work we've all put in, our economy has come a long way these past six years. Over the past 55 months, our businesses have added 10.3 million new jobs. For the first time in six years, the unemployment rate is below 6 percent. And on Thursday, we learned that over the past six months, our economy has grown at its fastest pace since 2003. But the gains of a growing economy aren't yet felt by everyone. So we've got to harness this momentum , and make the right choices so that everyone who works hard can get ahead. In recent weeks, I've talked about these choices, from raising the minimum wage to creating new...\n\nQ: Which is NOT included in the new policies that would help women and working families get ahead?", "options": ["Equal pay for equal work.", "Increase access to high-quality child care and paid family leave.", "Raise the minimum wage.", "Get rid of racial discrimination."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 360, "question": "Now that America has declared a state of swine flu public health emergency, you may be asking yourself -- what am Isupposed to do? Here is a list of practical steps you can take to prepare and protect yourself and your family. 1) Know the symptoms-- Here are some of the symptoms that sound like swine flu -- fevers over 100 degrees (37.8degC), body aches, cough, runny nose, and sometimes, nausea and diarrhea . It's also useful to know if you might have had an exposure either by recent travel to Mexico, or to the areas of known cases so far in America -- specific areas of California, Texas, New York, Ohio and Kansas. Or you may have been exposed to a sick person who came from those areas. 2) Don't panic-- If you have symptoms that sound like swine flu, do not rush to hospitals. Not only is t...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is one of the reasons why the disease is called \"Swine flu\"?", "options": ["Some patients have eaten some not-so-well-cooked pork.", "Some patients have contact with pigs in their life.", "The virus is probably developed from swine flu virus.", "The disease is mostly passed from pigs to humans."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1821, "question": "Earth Day events are arranged all over the world, but for New Yorkers in the Catskill region, there are plenty of options.s6t---- Earth Day Celebrations6t---- Place: Frost Valley; Time: Friday, April 8 - Saturday, April 9 (Check-in at 5:00 pm on Friday). Activities include recycled arts and crafts projects, classes on composting and recycling, nature hikes, and a greenhouse planting project. All ages are welcomed. $15.00 per person (includes lunch). Kids 5 and under free. Call (845) 985-2291 for more details and to register.s6t---- Earth Festivals6t---- Place: Milford Central School; Time: Saturday, April 9 (11:00 am - 3:00 pm). Enjoy exhibits, activities and entertainment. Bring along your recyclables to be collected. You'll go green! Fashion Show will be held at the end of the day. Admis...\n\nQ: If a couple with a five-year-old child go to Frost Valley, they should pay   _  .s6t----", "options": ["15 dollars", "20 dollars", "30 dollars", "35 dollarss6t----"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1387, "question": "Many years ago, when I was fresh out of school and working in Denver, I was driving to my parents' home in Missouri for Christmas. I stopped at a gas station about 50 miles from Oklahoma City, where I was planning to stop and visit a friend. While I was standing in line at the cash register , I said hello to an older couple who were also paying for gas. I took off, but had gone only a few miles when black smoke poured from the back of my car. I stopped and wondered what I should do. A car pulled up behind me. It was the couple I had spoken to at the gas station. They said they would take me to my friend's We chatted on the way into the city, and when I got out of the car, the husband gave me his business card. I wrote him and his wife a thank-you note for helping me. Soon afterward, I rece...\n\nQ: What happened when the author found smoke coming out of his car?", "options": ["He had it pulled back to the gas station.", "The couple sent him a business card.", "The couple offered to help him.", "He called his friend for help."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 481, "question": "I recently turned fifty, which is young for a tree, midlife for an elephant, and ancient for a sportsman. Fifty is a nice number for the states in the US or for a national speed limit but it is not a number that I was prepared to have hung on me. Fifty is supposed to be my father's age, but now I am stuck with this number and everything it means. A few days ago, a friend tried to cheer me up by saying, \" Fifty is what forty used to be.\" He had made an inspirational point, Am I over the hill?People keep telling me that the hill has been moved, and I keep telling them that he high-jump bar has dropped from the six feet I once easily cleared to the four feet that is impossible for me now. \" Your are not getting older, you are getting better.\" says Dr. Joyce Brothers. This, however, is the kin...\n\nQ: The author seems to tell us in Paragraph 1 that    _   .", "options": ["time alone will tell", "time goes by quickly", "time will show what is right", "time makes one forget the past"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2856, "question": "Sure, it's good to get along with your teacher because it makes that time you spend in the classroom more pleasant. And yes, it's good to get along with your teacher because, in general, it's smart to learn how to relate to the different types of people you'll meet throughout your life. But really, there's one super-important reason why you should get along with your teacher. Kids who get along with their teachers not only learn more, but they're more comfortable asking questions and getting extra help. This makes it easier to understand new material and do your best on tests. When you have this kind of relationship with a teacher, he or she can be someone to turn to with problems, such as problems with learning or school issues, such as bullying. As a kid in elementary or middle school, y...\n\nQ: What can we know from the passage?", "options": ["Kids are unable to understand lots of exciting information.", "Kids are bullied while communicating with others in schools.", "Kids will leave the class when not doing quite well with their teachers.", "Kids will leave the class when not satisfied with teachers' teaching methods."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3262, "question": "Dreams can be familiar and strange, fantastical or boring, but some dreams might be connected to the mental processes that help us learn. In a recent study, scientists found a connection between nap-time dreams and better memory in people who were learning a new skill. In the study,99 college students between the ages of 18 and 30 each spent an hour on a compute, trying to get through a virtual maze .The maze was different place each time they tired--making it even more difficult. They were also told to find a particular picture of a tree and remember where it was. For the first 90 minutes of a five-hour break, half of the participants stayed awake and an half were told to take a short nap .Participants who stayed awake were asked to describe their thoughts. Participants who took a nap wer...\n\nQ: Before having a short nap, participants of the experiment were asked to  _  .", "options": ["stay in a different place in the maze", "design a virtual maze which is difficult to get through", "experience the experiment and try to remember something", "get through a virtual maze on a computer from the same place"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2376, "question": "Tim Welford, aged 33, and Dom Mee, aged 30, both from England, were keen on (=\"like...\" very much) rowing boats. They made a plan to row across the Pacific Ocean from Japan to San Francisco. The name of their rowboat was \"Crackers\". It was about seven meters long. They set out from Japan on May 17,2001. They had rowed nearly 5,500 miles when their boat was hit by a fishing ship on September 17,2001. Luckily they both escaped unharmed, but their boat was badly damaged and they had to abandon( =\" stop)their\" journey. In a radio interview, Dom expressed his disappointment and explained how the accident took place. \"A fishing ship came towards us with nobody on the bridge and ran us down. It all happened so quickly. I managed to dive into the water. Tim felt it would be safer to stay on board....\n\nQ: 41. How long had Tim and Dom been at sea when their boat was hit by a fishing boat?", "options": ["For one month", "For two months.", "For three months.", "For four months."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 832, "question": "Homesick is a compound word made up of HOME and SICK.You know what each word means on its own, of course.But think about what the words mean when they are used together.Homesick means SICK FOR HOME. Now think for a minute about SEASICK.If you change the word home in the definition to the word sea, would the definition fit SEASICK? Seasick means SICK BY THE MOVEMENT ON THE SEA. When you are homesick ,the only place you want to be is at home.When you are seasick, the last place you want to be is at seA. Have you ever heard of a person being heartsick? Heartsick doesn't mean that something is wrong with a person's heart.people are heartsick when they are hurt deep inside and when they feel as if their hearts are broken. But, on the other hand, we have such compound words as handshake, handsta...\n\nQ: The word SEASICK means\"  _  \".", "options": ["to be eager to go to the sea", "what has nothing to do with the sea", "to be sick because of the sea", "that the sea is terrible"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2871, "question": "Both are so much related to each other. And both are so dissimilar! What are the differences between friendship and love? Is platonic friendship possible between persons of opposite sex? Let us try and understand. What is friendship? Why do we call a person our friend? When do we call someone a very good friend? If we care for a person, if we are always ready to help that person and if we share most of our thoughts with a person, they are our good friends. We can always count upon our good friends in an emergency. We are always sure that our friend will understand why we acted in a certain way. We need not explain anything to our very good friends. The friendship is so deep and the relationship is so close, that most of the things are automatically understood by our friends. What about lov...\n\nQ: What's the function of the first passage?", "options": ["To come up with the question for the further discussion.", "To explain the main idea of the following passage.", "To tell us the whole meaning of the passage.", "To advise us to make friends in different way."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1108, "question": "Joke l: A man was sitting reading his papers when his wife hit him round the head with a frying pan. \"What was that for?\" the man asked. The wife replied, \"That was for the piece of paper with the name Jenny on it I found in your pocket.\" The man then said, \"When l was at the races last week Jenny was the name of the horse I bet on.\" The wife apologized and went on with the housework. Three days later the man was watching TV when his wife hit him on the head with an even bigger frying pan, knocking him unconscious. Upon regaining consciousness the man asked why she had hit again. Wife replied, \"Your horse phoned.\" Joke 2: \"Do you believe in life after death?\" the boss asked one of his employees. \"Yes, sir, \" the new employee replied. \"Well, then, that makes everything just fine, \" the boss...\n\nQ: The wife became angry suddenly in Joke 1 because   _  .", "options": ["she had her frying pan burned while away", "her husband made a bet on a horse but lost", "her husband was carrying with himself a woman's name", "her husband's pocket money was lost without any reason"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2160, "question": "Borrowing to start a business is not easy. Getting a bank loan, particularly for a new small business, is _ Banks favor established-business people with a solid credit rating and a large bank account. They should also have experience in the business they propose to enter, and offer well-prepared business plans that show the ability to repay the loans. If you are not such a person, then you need to double your preparations to convince the banker to lend you that much needed start-up capital . If your business is new and small, bankers will need to know as much as possible about you and your business. However, many small business owners often make the mistake of not being well prepared when going to the bank to apply for the loan. Surprisingly, many loan applicants don't even have the slight...\n\nQ: The writer advises that before applying for a bank loan, the applicant should   _  .", "options": ["thoroughly prepare", "do some market research", "learn a lot about the bank", "know the upper limit of the loans"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2515, "question": "The interview had been going on for about 20 minutes and everything seems to be going well. Then,suddenly,the interviewer asks an unexpected question,\"Which is more important,law or Dove?\" Job applicants in the West increasingly find themselves asked strange questions like this. And the signs are that this is beginning to happen in China. Employers want people skilled,enthusiastic and devoted. So these are the qualities that any reasonably intelligent job applicants will try to show no matter what his or her actual feelings are. In response,employers are increasingly using questions which try and show the applicant's true personality. The question in the first paragraph comes from a test called the Keirsey Personality Sorter. It is an attempt to discover how people solve problems,rather th...\n\nQ: According to the writer, in an aptitude test, Chinese job applicants should  _  .", "options": ["not tell the truth", "learn to tell what they really think", "be more enthusiastic", "try to find out what the examiner really want to know"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3249, "question": "Most people buy a lot of gifts just before Christmas. But some people think we buy too much. They have started a special day called Buy Nothing Day. They don't want anyone to go shopping on that day. Buy Nothing Day is November 29. It's 25 days before Christmas. It's after Thanksgiving Day and often the first day of Christmas shopping. At this time, we see ads in Newspapers and on TV telling us to \"buy, buy, buy!\" The idea for Buy Nothing Day started in Vancouver, British Columbia. Now people all over the world celebrate Buy Nothing Day. In California, parents and children get together to read stories, sing songs, and paint pictures. The children talk about why they don't need a lot of toys. This year, in Manchester, England, people dressed up in costumes to tell people that we buy too muc...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT the day for people to celebrate Buy Nothing Day?", "options": ["November 29.", "25 days before Christmas.", "After Thanksgiving.", "The first day after Christmas."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2289, "question": "From their beginnings New England towns had a special democratic system of government. At a stated time all the citizens would assemble at a town meeting, where they would discuss local problems and express opinions freely. They also elected the town's officials at these gatherings and made decisions about the taxes they would pay and about other community matters. These meetings were usually held at the town hall, which was located in the central square. In the eighteenth-century town meetings, only men who owned property and who were church members actually voted, although everyone present was allowed to express their opinions. Later, all citizens were allowed to vote. Thus the town meeting became truly democratic. Town meetings are still common in New England communities. In recent year...\n\nQ: This passage mainly talks about   _  .", "options": ["the New England town meeting", "modern town meetings", "a democratic meeting", "New England towns"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2852, "question": "It was an extremely hot day. My younger brother Walt and I had decided to go swimming in a deep swimming hole across Mr. Blickez's farm and through some woods, because it would be the only way to cool ourselves down. The only problem with our plan was that this farm was guarded by a huge mean Hereford bull . Mr. Blickez had told us that Elsie was the meanest bull in town, maybe even in the county and we believed in him. But the hotter it got, the more we thought there was something _ about what he said. For one thing, we remembered Mr. Blickez liked telling tall tales; for another, Elsie seemed like a strange name for a bull. Finally, I talked Mom into asking permission for us to walk through the farm, and Mr. Blickez agreed. On our way across the farm, we stopped at the fence to admire th...\n\nQ: What was the problem faced by the author and his brother?", "options": ["They didn't know where to swim.", "They didn't know how to get to the stream.", "Their mother didn't want them to swim.", "They had to face a very mean bull."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1850, "question": "Depressed people can be very difficult to be around,and yet they need more than the usual amount of support and understanding from their friends and family. The anger and lack of concern that a depressed person may have for people close to him or her can be very disturbing to someone who's trying to help.At such times,the sincerity of a friend or a family member is questioned when the depressed person doesn't feel worthy of someone's friendship.Withdrawal from others can make it nearly impossible to encourage a depressed person to enter into activities that may help pull him or her out of the depression. It is frequently difficult for a depressed person to carry on a conversation.Attempts to help may be met with defensiveness and verbal attacks.While being supportive and understanding,the ...\n\nQ: .The above passage is mainly intended for   _  .", "options": ["a doctor who works with a depressed person", "a depressed person", "one who lives with a depressed person", "an expert who gives advice to a depressed person"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3107, "question": "When I was 18, I had a motorbike accident that put me in a coma for three months. The doctors said there was little chance of my coming out of it, but my identical twin, Marcus, didn't believe them and carried on talking to me. My first words when I came to myself were, \"Hello, Marcus. \"Even though I had no memory of my own name, or that the woman crying at my bedside was my mother, I knew Marcus immediately; it was like a genetic memory. just felt close to him. As weeks went by, I still could remember nothing before the accident. Marcus was the only person I could relate to. I had to relearn everything, and Marcus helped me. Because of my twin I wasn't scared of having lost my memory; I believed everything he said. He became my memory, telling me about my school, friends, previous girlfri...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for the text?", "options": ["My Twin Rewrote My Childhood", "An Accident Destroyed My Life", "Family Will Always Be with You", "Friends Share Everything"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2846, "question": "I want to let you know about an event that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Sunday morning. We decided to stop at a local gas station to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as if he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something to drink. However, it was not this that moved me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog lover, I noticed that the dog was a mother and that she had just had some puppies . She was hungry and weak and I felt so bad for her. I knew if she di...\n\nQ: The best title for this passage would be  _  .", "options": ["My Memory", "My wife and I", "Animals Are Parents Too", "A Mother Dog and Her Puppies"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2541, "question": "It's enough to give anyone an earache. Women spend an average of about five years on the phone during their working lives, research has shown. You won't be surprised to learn that women spend 18 months longer than men on the phone -- who only chat for an average of three years. Both sexes make and receive almost the same number of calls -- 277,000 for men and 288,000 for women. But women spend 13,500 more hours in total on their conversations. More than half of those chats are work-related but people spend on average twice as long on a personal call (10 minutes ) as on a business one. Despite the explosion in mobile phone ownership, most people still prefer to use landlines, the poll found. However, when people are tired of talking, the top excuse for getting a caller off the line is to sa...\n\nQ: From the text, we know that   _   .", "options": ["calls around midnight are acceptable to some people", "80% of people always refuse to answer a phone call", "people never ring the people in their address books", "Joseph Blass was one of the people who were polled"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1572, "question": "Immigration is the act of coming to a foreign country to live. The act of leaving one's country to settle in another is called emigration. Immigrants who flee their country because of persecution, war, or such disasters as famines or epidemics are known as refugees or displaced persons. Most people find it very hard to pull up roots in their native land and move to a strange country. But throughout history, countless millions of people have done so. The heaviest immigration worldwide took place from the early 1800's to the Great Depression, the economic hard times of the 1930's. In that period, about 60 million people moved to a new land. Most came from Europe. More than half immigrated to the United States. Other destinations included Canada, Argentina, Brazil, Australia, New Zealand, and...\n\nQ: There are altogether  _   reasons  of immigration listed in the passage.", "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2477, "question": "The United Nations says forty million people or so around the world went hungry in 2008, mainly because of higher food prices. Early estimates from the UN Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) show that 963 million people did not get enough to eat. World food prices have dropped since early 2008. Prices of major crops have decreased by more than half from their height earlier last year. But they remain high compared to earlier years. But FAO official Hafez Ghanem says lower prices have failed to end the food crisis in many poor countries. \"For millions in developing countries,\" he says, \"getting enough food every day to live an active and healthy life is a distant dream.\" The FAO says food shortage is a threat to people's health. Today, two-thirds of the world's _ people live in just a f...\n\nQ: Which country has not made progress in hunger reduction?", "options": ["North Korea", "Thailand", "Vietnam", "Ghana"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3428, "question": "I was at a busy traffic crossing waiting to cross to the other side. There was a family--a man, his wife and an old lady, waiting to cross with me. Then, the light turned green and all of us walked quickly across the road. The light lasted very short, and changed into red in no time. I noticed that both the man and his wife had crossed along with me and the old lady was left behind. I quickly realized what happened. When the light turned dreen again, I ran over to the other side, offered the old lady my right hand and we quickly walked together to the other side of the road. I used my left hand to stop any oncoming traffic so that even if the crossing signal turned red, we cuold make it to the other side safely. In the meantime, both the man and his wife realized that they had left the old...\n\nQ: The auther turned back to   _   .", "options": ["see what was happening", "keep the old lady safe", "look for the man and his wife", "help the old lady cross the road"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2414, "question": "John and Booby joined a wholesale company together just after graduation from college the same year. Both worked very hard. After several years, however, the boss promoted Bobby to the position of manager but John remained an ordinary employee . John could not take it any more, so he sent his resignation and complained that the boss did not value hard working workers but only promoted those who said good words of him. The boss knew that John worked very hard for the years. He thought for a moment and said, \"Thank you for telling me, but I have a request. I hope you will do one more thing for our company before you leave. Perhaps you will change your mind and take back your resignation.\" John agreed. The boss asked him to go and find out anyone selling watermelons in the market. John went a...\n\nQ: John wanted to stop his job in his company because  _  .", "options": ["Bobby was promoted but he was not", "he didn't want to say good words of his boss", "he thought the boss didn't take his hard work seriously", "he didn't want to be an ordinary employee"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2893, "question": "From Chengdu to Jiuzhaigou, you can travel along the East Line not only the other line going past Dujiangyan and Wenchuan. Take a regular bus from Chengdu Chengbei Bus Station from 9:00 to 16:30. It only takes about three hours to Jiangyou. The ticket is CNY50.00 net per person. Up along Fujiang River, you will pass the second largest city in Sichuan, Mianyang and enjoy the picturesque scenery. There is bus available to the destination from 6:30 to 13:30 in Mianyang Pingzheng Bus Station,The one way ticket is about CNY95.00 net per person. In this case, you can not get stop at Jiangyou and Pingwu. This is one option for you. In Jiangyou, visit the Former Residence of Li Bai, the famous poet in Tang Dynasty. If time permits, you can also take a look at the Doutuan Mountain, which is famous ...\n\nQ: If you take the bus from Pingzheng Bus Station to Jiuzhaigou, you can  _  .", "options": ["directly get to the destination", "get on the bus before 2 o'clock pm", "also visit Bao'en Temple halfway", "enjoy the scenery along Fujiang River"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1754, "question": "Having spent five years searching for her older brother, Miss Lund was unbelievable to think she had been working in the same building for five months. Mr.Philips, 33, and Miss Lund last saw each other almost twenty years ago after their father, also called Stephen, 56, lost contact with his son from a previous relationship.Miss Lund, only five at that time, moved to India with her father and mother Rose, while Steven lived with his mother in Wolverhapton. By the time Miss Lund and her parents returned to Leeds, the family had lost all contact with Mr.Philips.On turning 18, Lund started to track down her long-lost half brother, even asking customers at the shop where she worked.But despite checking on Internet sites such as Friends Reunited and MySpace, it wasn't until the pair started wor...\n\nQ: The relationship between the brother and sister is that  _  .", "options": ["they have the same father", "they have the same mother", "they have the same parents", "they are just cousins"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2183, "question": "The owner of an Alabama Chinese restaurant named \"Good Friend\" shot at a customer who complained about a fly in her eggroll Thursday night. The bullet narrowly missed 20-year-old Birmingham resident Jatari Walker who told the Daily News she is scarred by the entire experience. \"I can't sleep,\" she said Saturday afternoon. \"And since it happened I've had no appetite.\" Walker ordered a combination platter and eggroll from the Good Friend Chinese and Seafood Restaurant on Dennison Ave. Thursday evening. After paying her $7 bill she went back to her car and discovered a fly inside. \"I thought I need to take this back,\" she said. The customer went back and asked for a repayment and said the owner Chun HinChing, 52, was unhappy with her because she announced her discovery in front of other custo...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["this is the first time for Walker to buy food from Good Friend Restaurant", "the owner was unhappy with the complaint and refused to repay the money", "it is common for a restaurant owner in that neighborhood to have a weapon", "if someone had been hit, Ching would have been charged with attempted murder"], "answer": 2}]